// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Maria already … a piece of cake this morning.",
    answer: "ate",
    options: ["eat", "ate", "eaten", "eating"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "They … many reading books yesterday.",
    answer: "bought",
    options: ["buying", "buy", "bought", "buys"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "I … her when she … my girlfriend.",
    answer: "loved, was",
    options: ["loved, was", "love, were", "loved, were", "love, was"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "I … in Dauh Peken when I … in Bali.",
    answer: "lived, was",
    options: ["lived, were", "living, were", "living, was", "lived, was"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Many legit durians … … by us.",
    answer: "were opened",
    options: ["were opened", "was opening", "were opening", "was opened"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which sentence uses the simple past tense correctly?",
    answer: "He typed a letter yesterday.",
    options: [
      "He is typing a letter yesterday.",
      "He types a letter yesterday.",
      "He typed a letter yesterday.",
      "He was typing a letter yesterday.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "What is the correct form of the verb “to see” in the simple past tense for the pronoun “they”?",
    answer: "Saw",
    options: ["Seed", "Sees", "Saw", "See"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question:
      "What is the correct form of the verb “to come” in the simple past tense for the pronoun “I”?",
    answer: "Came",
    options: ["Comed", "Comes", "Came", "Come"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which sentence is not in the Simple Past Tense?",
    answer: "They are eating lunch now.",
    options: [
      "He went to the store yesterday.",
      "They are eating lunch now.",
      "I watched a movie last night.",
      "She visited her grandma last weekend.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which sentence is in the Simple Past Tense?",
    answer: "He played basketball with his friends yesterday.",
    options: [
      "They have been to China twice",
      "I am going to the park.",
      "She will sing at the concert tomorrow",
      "He played basketball with his friends yesterday.",
    ],
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
